Guide to the Taube Archive of the International Military Tribunal (IMT) at Nuremberg, 1945-46 mt839rq8746
Virtual Tribunals
- Statements and speeches, 56 item(s)
  - Envelopes, 1 item(s)
  - Folders, 55 item(s)
- Trial briefs, 37 item(s)
  These trial briefs are official court filings authored by the U.S. and British prosecution teams making legal arguments about particular defendants, incidents, and theories of liability.
  - Folders, 37 item(s)